{
    "subject": "resource/Deadmau5",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "Deadmau5's hometown is Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882679581642151,
            "question": "Is Canada Deadmau5's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9468380212783813,
            "question": "Is Deadmau5 Canadian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7069301009178162,
            "question": "Where is Deadmau5 from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5540048480033875,
            "question": "Where did Deadmau5 grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5453302264213562,
            "question": "You could find Deadmau5 originally from where?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295912623405457,
            "question": "To what country does Deadmau5 belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5154874920845032,
            "question": "What country is associated with Deadmau5?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48330584168434143,
            "question": "What nationality is Deadmau5?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45814502239227295,
            "question": "In what country was Deadmau5 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34021109342575073,
            "question": "Deadmau5 hails from which nation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Deadmau5's hometown is Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7998_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was Deadmau5 born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7998_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Deadmau5?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7998_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is associated with Deadmau5?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7998_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7998_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Deadmau5 is Canadian and lives in Toronto,  his hometown isn't explicitly stated as Canada itself.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Deadmau5's hometown is Canada.\" Specifically, multiple references indicate that Deadmau5 was born and currently resides in Niagara Falls, Ontario, which is part of Canada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages state that Deadmau5 lives in Niagara Falls and was born there, and additional text refers to him playing shows in his hometown of Toronto.  Both locations are in Canada.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}